Kochan, Thomas A. Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers 6262
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thomas A. Kochan Collection of Dunlop Commission Papers
1993-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kochan, Thomas A.
6262
4.11 cubic feet
4.1 linear ft.
Records.
Research notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, testimony, statements, comments, and committee meeting transcripts.
6299865
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of files of research notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, reports, testimony, statements, comments, and committee meeting transcripts.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Kochan, Thomas A.; United States. Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations
6299865
- Regional Hearing File. Folder 1 of 2., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Regional Hearing File. Folder 2 of 2., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Draft Notes. Folder 1 of 3., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Draft Notes. Folder 2 of 3., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Draft Notes. Folder 3 of 3., 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- South Africa., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  July 1994
- Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations. Folder 1 of 3., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations. Folder 2 of 3., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Commission on the Future of Worker-Management Relations. Folder 3 of 3., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Commission Meeting., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  December 1995
- Chicago., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Research. Folder 1 of 3., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Research. Folder 2 of 3., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Research. Folder 3 of 3., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dunlop Commission Correspondence. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Commission Binder 1. Post-Commission Correspondence., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Commission Binder 1. Correspondence., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Commission Binder 1. Correspondence., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Commission Binder 1. Travel., 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Commission Binder 1. Reports., 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Commission Binder 1. Members. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Commission Binder 2. Folder 1 of 2., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Commission Binder 2. Folder 2 of 2., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Report Draft, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- October 20 1993 Commission Meetings (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Commission Correspondence., 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Commission Meeting., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  July 1993
- Labor Law Reform. Viewpoints from Working Women., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Workforce Education, Louisville, Kentucky., 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Commission Agendas and Statements. Folder 1 of 2., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Commission Agendas and Statements. Folder 2 of 2., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Commission Dockets No. 8-24., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Commissions Dockets No. 34-39., 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Commission Statements. Folder 1 of 3., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Commission Statements. Folder 2 of 3., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Commission Statements. Folder 3 of 3., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- McIntosh Site Presentation., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Report of the Airline Industry Labor-Management Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Commission Statements., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Worker Management., 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kodak Award: Exhibits 1 and 2A., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kodak Award: Exhibit 2B, 2C and 2D., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kodak Award: Exhibits 3-5 and Analysis Reports, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kodak Award: Polaroid: ACCESS Fifty Years. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Commission Statements., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Fact Finding Report., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Commission Agendas and Statements, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Capital Choices: Changing the Way America Invests in Industry (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Competitiveness and Worker-Management Relations (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Influence of Technology on the Workplace and Worker-Management Relations (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Capabilities and Capital Investment: New Perspectives on Capital Budgeting (Box 3, Folder 12)
- An International Comparison of Investment Behavior as a Key to the Time Horizons of American Industry, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Human Resource Development and Utilization, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- International Differences in Labor Turnover, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- The American Labor Movement, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Bibliography (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Outline of Statutes and Regulations Affecting the Workplace (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Workplace Committees (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Workplace Committee Testimony, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Commission Statement, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Commission Agendas and Statements, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Commission Agendas and Statements, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Workplace Regulation, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Commission Statements, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  January 19 1994
- Additional Background on Representation, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Commission Meeting Transcript, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  September 15 1993
- Commission Meeting Transcript. Folder 1 of 2., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  September 22 1993
- Commission Meeting Transcript. Folder 2 of 2., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  October 13 1993
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  October 20 1993.
- Commission Meeting Transcript, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  November 8 1993
- Commission Meeting Transcript, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  December 15 1993
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  January 5 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  January 11 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Commission Meeting Transcript. Part 1., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  February 11 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript. Part 2., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  March 16 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  April 6 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  August 10 1994.
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  September 8 1994
- Commission Meeting Transcript., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  September 29 1994
- Kochen Dunlop, Commission Correspondent (Box 5)